Guide to the Edith McChesney Ker papers, 1948-2003
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
- St. Petersburg-Stockholm-Archipelago #2, July 2001 (Box 19, Folder 24)
- St. Petersburg-Stockholm-Archipelago #2, July 2001 (Box 19, Folder 25)
- St. Petersburg-Stockholm-Archipelago #2, July 2001 (Box 19, Folder 26)
- St. Petersburg-Stockholm-Archipelago #2, July 2001 (Box 19, Folder 27)
- St. Petersburg-Stockholm-Archipelago #2, July 2001 (Box 19, Folder 28)
- St. Petersburg-Stockholm-Archipelago #2, July 2001 (Box 19, Folder 29)
- St. Petersburg-Stockholm-Archipelago #2, July 2001 (Box 19, Folder 30)
- Pacific Northwest, September 2002 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Pacific Northwest, September 2002 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Pacific Northwest, September 2002 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Pacific Northwest, September 2002 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Pacific Northwest, September 2002 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Pacific Northwest, September 2002 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Pacific Northwest, September 2002 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  9 Slides; Color
- Notes on Victoria and Vancouver, circa 2002 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Western Cruises #1, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Western Cruises #1, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Western Cruises #1, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Western Cruises #1, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Western Cruises #1, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Western Cruises #1, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Western Cruises #1, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Western Cruises #2, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Western Cruises #2, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Western Cruises #2, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Western Cruises #2, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Western Cruises #2, July 1983 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  13 Slides; Color
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #1, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #1, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #1, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #1, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #1, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #1, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #1, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #2, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #2, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #2, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #2, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #2, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #2, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #2, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #3, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #3, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #3, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Passage Through History 4-5/93 #3, April-May 1993 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  6 Slides; Color
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #1 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #1 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #1 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #1 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #1 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #1 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #1 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #2 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #2 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #2 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #2 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #2 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #2 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #2 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #3 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Holland-Belgium 1992 #3 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Holland Notes, circa 1992 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- France 1985 #1 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- France 1985 #1 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- France 1985 #1 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- France 1985 #1 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- France 1985 #1 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- France 1985 #1 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- France 1985 #1 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- France 1985 #2 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- France 1985 #2 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- France 1985 #2 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- France 1985 #2 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- France 1985 #2 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- France 1985 #2 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- France 1985 #2 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Notes on France, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Finland-Norway, July 2000 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Finland-Norway, July 2000 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Finland-Norway, July 2000 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Finland-Norway, July 2000 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Finland-Norway, July 2000 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Finland-Norway, July 2000 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Finland-Norway, July 2000 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Notes on Finland-Norway, circa 2000 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Scandinavia 1987 #1 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Scandinavia 1987 #1 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Scandinavia 1987 #1 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Scandinavia 1987 #1 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Scandinavia 1987 #1 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Scandinavia 1987 #1 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Scandinavia 1987 #1 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Scandinavia 1987 #2 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Scandinavia 1987 #2 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Scandinavia 1987 #2 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Scandinavia 1987 #2 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Scandinavia 1987 #2 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Scandinavia 1987 #2 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Scandinavia 1987 #2 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Scandinavia 1987 #2 (Box 23, Folder 23)
  2 Slides; Color
- Scandinavia Notes, circa 1987 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Italy November 1999 #1 (Box 24, Folder 1)
- Italy November 1999 #1 (Box 24, Folder 2)
- Italy November 1999 #1 (Box 24, Folder 3)
- Italy November 1999 #1 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Italy November 1999 #1 (Box 24, Folder 5)
- Italy November 1999 #1 (Box 24, Folder 6)
- Italy November 1999 #1 (Box 24, Folder 7)
- Italy November 1999 #2 (Box 24, Folder 8)
- Italy November 1999 #2 (Box 24, Folder 9)
- Italy November 1999 #2 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  4 Slides; Color
- Notes on Italy, circa 1999 (Box 24, Folder 11)
- Switzerland 1983 #1, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 12)
- Switzerland 1983 #1, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 13)
- Switzerland 1983 #1, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 14)
- Switzerland 1983 #1, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 15)
- Switzerland 1983 #1, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 16)
- Switzerland 1983 #1, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Switzerland 1983 #1, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 18)
- Switzerland 1983 #2, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 19)
- Switzerland 1983 #2, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 20)
- Switzerland 1983 #2, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 21)
- Switzerland 1983 #2, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 22)
- Switzerland 1983 #2, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 23)
- Switzerland 1983 #2, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 24)
- Switzerland 1983 #2, September 1983 (Box 24, Folder 25)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #1), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #1), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #1), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 3)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #1), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 4)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #1), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 5)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #1), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 6)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #1), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #2), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #2), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 9)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #2), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 10)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #2), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 11)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #2), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 12)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #2), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 13)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #2), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 14)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #3), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 15)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #3), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 16)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #3), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 17)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #3), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 18)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #3), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 19)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995 (Carousel #3), August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 20)
- Namibia-Zimbabwe Notes, circa August 1995 (Box 25, Folder 21)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 1)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 2)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 3)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 5)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 7)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 8)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 9)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 10)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 11)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 12)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 13)
- SWA/Botswana, August 1984 (Box 26, Folder 14)
- Egypt March 1996 #1 (Box 26, Folder 15)
- Egypt March 1996 #1 (Box 26, Folder 16)
- Egypt March 1996 #1 (Box 26, Folder 17)
- Egypt March 1996 #1 (Box 26, Folder 18)
- Egypt March 1996 #1 (Box 26, Folder 19)
- Egypt March 1996 #1 (Box 26, Folder 20)
- Egypt March 1996 #1 (Box 26, Folder 21)
- Egypt March 1996 #2 (Box 26, Folder 22)
- Egypt March 1996 #2 (Box 26, Folder 23)
- Egypt March 1996 #2 (Box 26, Folder 24)
- Egypt March 1996 #2 (Box 26, Folder 25)
- Egypt March 1996 #2 (Box 26, Folder 26)
- Egypt March 1996 #2 (Box 26, Folder 27)
- Egypt March 1996 #2 (Box 26, Folder 28)
- Notes on Egypt, circa March 1996 (Box 26, Folder 29)
- Safari I #1, 1962-1972 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Safari I #1, 1962-1973 (Box 27, Folder 2)
- Safari I #1, 1960-1973 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Safari I #1, 1962-1972 (Box 27, Folder 4)
- Safari I #1, 1960-1973 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Safari I #1, 1962-1972 (Box 27, Folder 6)
- Safari I #1, 1962-1973 (Box 27, Folder 7)
- Safari I #1, 1962-1972 (Box 27, Folder 8)
- Safari I #2, 1962-1973 (Box 27, Folder 9)
- Safari I #2, 1963-1973 (Box 27, Folder 10)
- Safari I #2, 1962-1973 (Box 27, Folder 11)
- Safari I #2, 1970-1976 (Box 27, Folder 12)
- Safari I #2, 1963-1973 (Box 27, Folder 13)
- Safari I #2, 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 14)
- Safari II #1, 1960-1973 (Box 27, Folder 15)
- Safari II #1, 1964-1973 (Box 27, Folder 16)
- Safari II #1, 1960-1973 (Box 27, Folder 17)
- Safari II #1, 1963-1969 (Box 27, Folder 18)
- Safari II #1, 1962-1972 (Box 27, Folder 19)
- Safari II #1, August 1958; 1963-1973 (Box 27, Folder 20)
- Safari II #1, 1965-1973 (Box 27, Folder 21)
- Safari II #2, 1962-1973 (Box 27, Folder 22)
- Safari II #2, 1962-1973 (Box 27, Folder 23)
- Safari II #2, 1963-1973 (Box 27, Folder 24)
- Safari II #2, 1962-1976 (Box 27, Folder 25)
- Safari II #2, 1965-1974 (Box 27, Folder 26)
- Safari II #2, 1965-1971 (Box 27, Folder 27)
- Safari II #2, 1966-1971 (Box 27, Folder 28)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #1 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #1 (Box 28, Folder 2)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #1 (Box 28, Folder 3)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #1 (Box 28, Folder 4)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #1 (Box 28, Folder 5)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #1 (Box 28, Folder 6)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #1 (Box 28, Folder 7)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #2 (Box 28, Folder 8)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #2 (Box 28, Folder 9)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #2 (Box 28, Folder 10)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #2 (Box 28, Folder 11)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #2 (Box 28, Folder 12)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #2 (Box 28, Folder 13)
- UK Cruise June 1991 #2 (Box 28, Folder 14)
- UK Cruise June 1991 1-53 #3 (Box 28, Folder 15)
- UK Cruise June 1991 1-53 #3 (Box 28, Folder 16)
- UK Cruise June 1991 1-53 #3 (Box 28, Folder 17)
- Notes for UK Cruise, June 1991 (Box 28, Folder 18)
- Scotland September 1999 #1 (Box 28, Folder 19)
- Scotland September 1999 #1 (Box 28, Folder 20)
- Scotland September 1999 #1 (Box 28, Folder 21)
- Scotland September 1999 #1 (Box 28, Folder 22)
- Scotland September 1999 #1 (Box 28, Folder 23)
- Scotland September 1999 #1 (Box 28, Folder 24)
- Scotland September 1999 #1 (Box 28, Folder 25)
- Scotland September 1999 #2 (Box 28, Folder 26)
- Scotland September 1999 #2 (Box 28, Folder 27)
- Scotland September 1999 #2 (Box 28, Folder 28)
- Notes on Scotland, September 1999 (Box 28, Folder 29)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 1)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 2)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 3)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 4)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 5)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 6)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 7)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 8)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 9)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 10)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 11)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 12)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 13)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 14)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 15)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 16)
- 1958 Africa Trip, August-October 1958 (Box 29, Folder 17)
- 1964 Africa Cruise, May-June 1964 (Box 29, Folder 18)
- 1964 Africa Cruise, May-June 1964 (Box 29, Folder 19)
- Safari Groups, People, Misc. Scenery, Camps, 1963-1969 (Box 29, Folder 20)
- Safari Groups, People, Misc. Scenery, Camps, 1962-1964 (Box 29, Folder 21)
- Faded but Rare, circa 1960s (Box 29, Folder 22)
- Edward G. Robinson, May 1952 (Box 29, Folder 23)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #1, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 1)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #1, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 2)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #1, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 3)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #1, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 4)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #1, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 5)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #1, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #1, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 7)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #2, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 8)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #2, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 9)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #2, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #2, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 11)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #2, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 12)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #2, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 13)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #2, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 14)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #3, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 15)
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji #3, November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 16)
- Notes about Australia, New Zealand, Fiji, circa November 1987 (Box 30, Folder 17)
- New Zealand, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 18)
- New Zealand, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 19)
- New Zealand, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 20)
- New Zealand, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 21)
- New Zealand, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 22)
- New Zealand, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 23)
- New Zealand, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 24)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 1)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 2)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 3)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 4)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 5)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 6)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 7)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 8)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 9)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 10)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 11)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 12)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 13)
- Spitsbergen, July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 14)
- Notes on Spitsbergen, circa July 1994 (Box 31, Folder 15)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #1, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #1, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 2)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #1, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #1, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 4)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #1, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #1, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 6)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #1, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 7)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #2, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #2, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 9)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #2, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 10)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #2, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #2, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 12)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #2, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #2, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 14)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #3, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 15)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #3, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #3, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #3, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #3, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 19)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #3, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 20)
- Namibia-Botswana 1989 #3, September-October 1989 (Box 32, Folder 21)
- Europe II- ex. U.K., Botswana, Safari 1960, Lisbon, Paris, Holland, Portugal, June 1961 (Box 33, Folder 1)
- Europe II- ex. U.K., Botswana, Safari 1960, Lisbon, Paris, Holland, Portugal, June 1961; October 1954 (Box 33, Folder 2)
- Europe II- ex. U.K., Botswana, Safari 1960, Lisbon, Paris, Holland, Portugal, October 1954; May 1971 (Box 33, Folder 3)
- Europe II- ex. U.K., Botswana, Safari 1960, Lisbon, Paris, Holland, Portugal, May 1971; December 1960 (Box 33, Folder 4)
- Europe II- ex. U.K., Botswana, Safari 1960, Lisbon, Paris, Holland, Portugal, December 1960 (Box 33, Folder 5)
- Europe II- ex. U.K., Botswana, Safari 1960, Lisbon, Paris, Holland, Portugal, December 1960; March 1962 (Box 33, Folder 6)
- Middle East I, October 1952-September 1954 (Box 33, Folder 7)
- Middle East I, September 1952-September 1954 (Box 33, Folder 8)
- Middle East I, 1952-1955 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Middle East I, January 1953-November 1953 (Box 33, Folder 10)
- Middle East I, January 1953-September 1954 (Box 33, Folder 11)
- Middle East I, August 1953-July 1954 (Box 33, Folder 12)
- Middle East I, October 1952; October 1953-September 1954 (Box 33, Folder 13)
- Middle East I, October 1952-September 1954 (Box 33, Folder 14)
- Middle East I, June 1953-June 1954 (Box 33, Folder 15)
- Middle East I, June 1953-June 1954 (Box 33, Folder 16)
- Middle East I, October 1953-April 1954 (Box 33, Folder 17)
- Middle East I, April 1953-October 1953; September 1954 (Box 33, Folder 18)
- Middle East I, April 1953 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  1 Slide; Color
- Galapagos Islands and Grand Tetons, 1972 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  800 ft. Reel, 16mm Color Reversal
- U.S.A. and Canadian Parks, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 2)
- Alaska 1986, 1990, Alaska III (Box 35, Folder 1)
  Photographs, Postcards, Brochures
- Argentina 1991; Argentina-Chile-Easter Island 1993, 1991; 1993 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  Itinerary, Photographs, Postcards, Articles, Notes
- Holland-Belgium 1992; Passage Through History 1993, 1992; 1993 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  Itinerary, Photographs, Postcards, Brochures
- Namibia-Zimbabwe 1995; Egypt March 1996, 1995; March 1996 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  Photographs, Postcards, Itinerary
- Eastern Europe 1996; Central Europe Danube Cruise 1997; Everglades 1998, 1996-1998 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  Articles, Photographs, Postcards, Itinerary
- Namibia-Botswana August 1984, September-October 1989 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  Postcards, Photographs, Itinerary, Brochures
- Turkey 1994; Spitsbergen 1994; Nova Scotia 1994 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  Itinerary, Photographs, Postcards, Articles, Brochures
- Baja 1984-1985; Polar Bears 1985 (Box 39, Folder 1)
- Africa, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  Maps, Articles, Brochures, Itinerary, Cards
- Montreal; Virginia Caves; Florida; Amboseli, Kenya; D.C. Zoo; Spring in Alexandria; St.Petersburg-Stockholm-Archipelago; Canadian Rockies, August-December 2001 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  Programs, Articles, Photographs, Postcards
- Arizona 2002: Tucson (Tanque Verde Ranch) and Sonora Desert; The Best of the Pacific Northwest 2003: Seattle, Washington, Victoria, B.C., and Duncan, Chemainus, Whistler, Vancouver (B.C.); Cruise the Passage of Peter the Great (Cruise Between St. Petersburg and Moscow) 2003, 2002-2003 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  Photographs, Postcards, Brochures, Itinerary
- Australia, New Zealand, Fiji, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  Pictures, Brochures, Postcards, Itinerary
- Scandinavia, 1987 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  Maps, Itinerary, Pictures, Postcards
- Gaspe, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  Maps, Pictures, Brochures, Articles
- Canyons of Time 1990; U.K. Cruise 1991, 1990; 1991 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  Articles, Pictures, Brochures, Itinerary
- Articles and Writings, 1949-2003 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  Writings and articles; some written by Edie Ker.
- Safari Pictures, 1950s-2003 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  Small and medium images of safari and personal photos.
- Safari Pictures, 1950s-2003 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  Medium and large images from safari.
- Safari Pictures, 1950s-2003 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  Small and medium images from safari.
- Safari Pictures, 1950s-2003 (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Safari Pictures, 1950s-2003 (Box 49, Folder 1)